schwinnbike.com 2003-06-25

# Schwinn Heritage

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
PACIFIC is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet. We believe that it is important you know how we treat the information about you that we receive via the Site.

In general, you may visit the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about you. Our servers capture, but do not collect, the IP addresses, domain names and network identifiers of our users. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the Site, pages viewed, etc. PACIFIC uses this information to measure the use of our Site and to improve the content of our Site. E-mail addresses and other personally identifiable information such as first and last name, home or other physical address, telephone number and other similar information are known only when voluntarily provided by a visitor for registration for sweepstakes, contests or other participation of visitors in any available online interactive activities.

Unless otherwise disclosed during the collection, personally identifiable information that may be collected in connection with visitors to this Site is retained by PACIFIC or subsidiary corporations ("Affiliates"). PACIFIC and our Affiliates do not sell, transfer or otherwise disclose this personally identifiable information outside those companies, except where disclosure is required by law.

We may use the personal information you provide for any of the following purposes: (1) to understand the use of our Site and make improvements; (2) to fulfill prizes; (3) to respond to specific requests from visitors; (4) to obtain parental consent from visitors under 18 years of age, where necessary; (5) to provide any necessary notices to our visitors or their parent or guardians, where necessary; (6) to protect the security or integrity of our Site when necessary; (7) to send you notices and solicitations regarding Site and our businesses; and (8) in general to promote and market our products to you. These solicitations may take the form of mailings via U.S. mail or other couriers, telephone calls, e-mail solicitations and other methods of contact. If you do not want to receive these solicitations from us using your personally identifiable information, you may specify this during registration, or you may notify us by contacting Pacific Cycle, C/O Webmaster, 100 Fairway Dr., Suite 100, Vernon Hills, IL 60061.

It is our policy that visitors to our Site who are under the age of 18 should not post on or provide information to our Site without the consent of their parents. You should supervise the online activities of your children, and consider the use of parental control tools available from online services and software providers that help provide a kid-friendly Internet environment.

A technology called "cookies" may be used to provide you with tailored information. A "cookie" is a tiny element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. You may be able to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Our cookies collect the operating system and browser that a visitor is using.

This Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.

This Site may contain links to other sites of third parties. We are not responsible for the content of privacy practices of those other sites.

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. You are responsible for checking this policy when you visit our Site to review the current policy. If you do not agree with the policy, you should cease use of the Site immediately.
